In the Fire is a thriller, drama, horror film directed by Conor Allyn.
A doctor from New York travels to a remote plantation in the 1890s to care
for a disturbed boy who seems to have inexplicable abilities.
She begins treating the child, but in doing so, ignites a war between science and religion as the local
priest believes the boy is possessed by the devil and the cause of the village's woes.
Grace Burnham, played by Amber Heard.
Nicolas Marquez, played by Eduardo Noriega.
Martin Marquez, played by Lorenzo McGovern Zaini.
Antonio, played by Luca Calvani.
Temo, played by Herbert Ignacio.
Maria, played by Monica Contini.
In the Fire is a 2023 thriller film directed by Conor Allyn, from a
screenplay by Allyn, Pascal Borno and Silvio Muraglia.
It stars Amber Heard, Eduardo Noriega and Lorenzo McGovern Zaini.
It had its world premiere at the Taormina Film Festival on June 24, 2023, and was
released in the United States on October 13, 2023, by Saban Films.
The film explores themes of village, supernatural,
possession, priest, demonic possession.
The tone is dark and emotional and intense.